A Guide to the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Secretary of Public Safety Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981)
The Library of Virginia
31516
35 cu. ft. (35 boxes)
Virginia Secretary of Public Safety
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and other protected information is considered confidential and restricted from public access for 75 years. It may be necessary for an archivist to review any unprocessed, modern record collections (those collections less than 75 years old) that may contain confidential information before the records can be used by patrons for research purposes or before any copies of records can be made for patrons. If you are planning to use these records, please contact Archives Reference Services for more details before planning your research trip.
If a request for copies is made for material containing confidential information, it is understood that this information will be redacted from the copies, if it is possible to do so. If redaction is not possible, the records will be withheld. Researchers must also agree that no direct or indirect contact will be made with the individuals to whom any personal or confidential information relates. Improper use and/or re-disclosure of privacy protected information is a breach of confidentiality which could result in the loss of access to the archival collections housed and maintained by The Library of Virginia, and could result in legal penalties (Code of Virginia, 18.2-186.3).
Acquisition Information
Accession 31516 transferred by Audrey B. Burton, Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, Ninth Street Office Building, Richmond, Va., 7 October 1982.
Historical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governors top management team or "secretariats," as they are called now. Governor Linwood Holton's top priority for the 1972 session of the General Assembly was a proposal for a Governor's Cabinet, reorganizing state agencies into six major departments, each headed by a secretary appointed by the governor. Transportation and public safety was one of these six departments. The office of Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety was created on April 8, 1972, by an act passed by the General Assembly.
Governor Holton appointed Wayne A. Whitham, a member of the Winchester City Council, as the first Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety. Secretary Whitham took office on July 1, 1972, and was responsible for State Highway Commission, Divsion of Motor Vehicles, Department of State Police, Highway Safety Division, Office of Emergency Services, Department of Military Affairs, Virginia State Crime Commission and the Law Enforcement Officers Training Standards Commission. The Office has undergone a series of administrative reorganizations since. On April 12, 1976, the Legislature established separate secretariats for transportation and for public safety, effective July 1, 1976.
Wayne A. Whitham, the first Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, was reappointed by Governor-elect Miles E. Godwin, Jr., in December 1973. On June 10, 1976, Governor Godwin appointed H. Selwyn Smith, a former Prince William County commonwealth's attorney (1960-1968) and former state senator (1972-1975), as the first Secretary of Public Safety. Smith was reappointed by Governor-elect John N. Dalton in December 1977. Smith resigned effective July 1, 1980 after he was appointed judge of the 31st Judicial Circuit of Virginia. Governor Dalton named T. Rodman Layman, an Alcoholic Beverage and Control Board Commissioner (1970-1980), to succeed Smith as Secretary of Public Safety. Layman served until the end of Dalton's term in January 1982.
Scope and Content
Contains a variety of correspondence and subject files relating to the agencies and boards that were under the supervision of the Secretary of Public Safety. Files include those related to activities of the Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, the Department of Corrections, and the State Police. The records also include fire safety inspections, state and federal legislation files, budget and capital outlay documents, and records on a variety of other public safety-related topics. Most of the material is in the form of correspondence, memorandums, and reports.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the one series:
Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981)
The original order of this material during its use is unknown. Whether the current physical order is indeed the original order, remains undetermined as well. There is no readily apparent series structure or other arrangement method. The physical arrangement of this collection has been maintained, but arrangement in the finding aid is alphabetical by folder title.
Contents List
- Director's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1971-1982 (bulk 1976-1981). (Box 1-35.)
  - Action/VISTA, 1979. (Box 2)
  - Addendum Proposals: 1980-1982 Biennium, 1979. (Box 5)
  - Addendum Requests: 1980-1982 Biennium, 1979-1980. (Box 5)
  - Administration and Finance: Miscellaneous, 1979-1980. (Box 31)
  - AFL-CIO, 1976. (Box 2)
  - Agency General Fund Target: Rehabilitative School Authority (1978-1980 Biennium) [2 folders], 1977. (Box 6)
  - Agency Guidance Memorandums, 1979. (Box 9)
  - Agency Heads, Memos to, 1980-1982. (Box 2)
  - Agency Procurement Requests, 1978-1979. (Box 21)
  - Agency Procurement Requests, 1978-1980. (Box 21)
  - Agency Procurement Requests, 1979-1980. (Box 5)
  - Agency Regulations, 1980-1981. (Box 2)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1976-1978. (Box 27)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Commission: General, 1979. (Box 27)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Commission: General, 1980. (Box 35)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of, 1981. (Box 10)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Audits, 1977-1978. (Box 35)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Automobiles, 1980. (Box 35)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Data Processing (POS ADP-1 Package), 1977-1979. (Box 10)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Data Processing (POS System), 1977-1979. (Box 10)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Edwards Complaint (E.E.O.), 1980. (Box 35)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Exmore Store (Northampton County), 1979. (Box 27)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Financial System, 1976-1978. (Box 10)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Gate City Store, 1979. (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: General [empty folder], undated. (Box 10)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Investigation and Enforcement, Div. of, 1976-1978. (Box 27)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Investigations and Complaints, 1977-1978. (Box 35)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Litter, Throw-Away Containers, 1977-1979. (Box 27)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Loan, 1977-1978. (Box 27)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Merge of Enforcement Division, undated. (Box 27)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Military Reservations, 1979. (Box 27)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Minor Awareness Program, 1976-1980. (Box 35)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Mount Jackson Store, 1979. (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Notices, Bulletins, Letters, Resolutions, 1977-1981. (Box 27)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Ocean View Relocation Proposal, 1976-1977. (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Operating Schedule for Stores, 1979. (Box 35)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Personnel Positions and Regrades, 1978-1980. (Box 35)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Proposed Store at Manassass Park Shopping Center, 1977. (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Purcellville Store, 1979. (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Retail Store Replacement (Falls Church), 1978-1979. (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Smyth County, 1979. (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Tax-Exempt Equipment Lease Financing, 1979. (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Warrenton, 1979. (Box 7)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of: Wise County, 1979. (Box 7)
  - Allotment Guidelines: 4th Quarter, 1976-1977. (Box 9)
  - Analysis of Alternatives, 1978-1981. (Box 2)
  - Appalachian Learning Center, 1979-1981. (Box 8)
  - Appropriations: 1980-1982 Biennium, 1980-1981. (Box 5)
  - Appropriations Committee: 1978 General Assembly (RE: Enterprises), 1977-1978. (Box 8)
  - Appropriations Committee Meeting, 1979. (Box 33)
  - Appropriations: Presentation to House Committee (1980-1982 Biennium), 1979. (Box 5)
  - Architectural Barriers: Transition Plan for Removing, 1977. (Box 6)
  - Arlington Detention Center, 1978. (Box 31)
  - Audit Reports, 1976-1977. (Box 14)
  - Audit Reports, 1978-1981. (Box 2)
  - Automated Data Processing (ADP) Procurement Manual, 1978-1981. (Box 5)
  - Biennium Budget Execution: PROBUD, 1980-1982, 1980. (Box 9)
  - Bland Correctional Center, 1976-1981. (Box 8)
  - Board of Inquiry: Ferguson Case, 1978-1979. (Box 7)
  - Budget Amendments/Adjustments, 1977. (Box 29)
  - Budget: Automated Data Processing (Preparation and Review for 1980-1982 Biennium), 1978-1979. (Box 5)
  - Budget: Commonwealth's Attorney's Services and Training Council (1980-1982 Biennium), 1980. (Box 5)
  - Budget: Department of Corrections (1980-1982 Biennium), 1979-1981. (Box 5)
  - Budget: Department of Corrections (1980-1982 Biennium), 1978-1981. (Box 9)
  - Budget: Fire Services Commission (1978-1980 Biennium), 1978. (Box 5)
  - Budget: FY 1978-1980, 1977-1978. (Box 30)
  - Budget: General (1980-1982 Biennium), 1979-1980. (Box 9)
  - Budget Material: Public Safety (FY 1978-1980), 1977-1978. (Box 30)
  - Budget: Preparation and Submission of 1978-1980 Biennial Budget Letters, 1977-1978. (Box 6)
  - Budget: Program Monitoring Procedures (1980-1982 Biennium), 1980. (Box 5)
  - Budget: Public Safety Agencies (1980-1982 Biennium), undated. (Box 5)
  - Budget: Public Safety, Office of, 1976. (Box 12)
  - Budget: Public Safety, Office of, 1978-1981. (Box 9)
  - Budget: Rehabilitative School Authority (1980-1982 Biennium), [2 folders], 1979. (Box 5)
  - Budget: State Police (1980-1982 Biennium), 1981. (Box 5)
  - Budget Bill: 1981, 1980. (Box 9)
  - Budget Bill: Recommended Amendments to 1978 Appropriation Act, undated. (Box 9)
  - Budget Cycle: Public Safety Agencies (1980-1982), 1978-1980. (Box 9)
  - Budget Requests: 10% Reduction (1978-1980 Biennium), 1977. (Box 6)
  - Budget Review, 1977-1978. (Box 30)
  - Budget Review: Appendix O, 1977. (Box 30)
  - Cabinet Secretaries: General, 1979-1981. (Box 28)
  - Capital Outlay: Corrections, Dept. of, 1977-1981. (Box 9)
  - Capital Outlay: General, 1976-1980. (Box 9)
  - Capital Outlay: Personnel, 1980-1981. (Box 24)
  - Capital Outlay: Public Safety (1980-1982 Biennium), 1981. (Box 5)
  - Capital Outlay: Requests, 1980-1982. (Box 5)
  - Capital Outlay: State Police, 1976-1979. (Box 24)
  - Capital Outlay: State Police, 1980-1982. (Box 5)
  - Capitol Police, 1977-1978. (Box 27)
  - Capitol Police, 1979-1981. (Box 27)
  - Central Criminal Records Exchange, 1977. (Box 32)
  - Central Garage Pool: Types of Disciplinary Action, 1977-1980. (Box 2)
  - Central State, 1977-1979. (Box 26)
  - CETA, 1978-1981. (Box 2)
  - Children: Emotionally Disturbed (Mental Health and Corrections), 1977-1982. (Box 3)
  - Children: Placement of Virginia Children Outside of Virginia, 1976-1977. (Box 7)
  - Children's Rights Report, 1978. (Box 14)
  - Chronological File, 1980. (Box 24)
  - Citizens Coalition for Criminal Justice Committee, 1975-1977. (Box 33)
  - Civil Rights Reorganization, President's Task Force on, 1978. (Box 3)
  - Climatological Program, State, 1977. (Box 3)
  - CO-1 Forms: Capital Outlay, 1976-1979. (Box 9)
  - Coal Fields / Coal Strike (3 folders), 1977-1978. (Box 14)
  - Coal-Fired Boilers, 1977-1979. (Box 33)
  - Coffey, Roger, (Rev.), 1977. (Box 33)
  - Colleges: Miscellaneous, 1979-1980. (Box 3)
  - Commission for Children and Youth, 1977. (Box 14)
  - Commonwealth Accounting and Reporting System, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Commonwealth Resource Center, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Commonwealth's Attorney's Services and Training Council, 1979. (Box 7)
  - Commonwealth's Attorney's Services and Training Council: Cale, James A., Jr. (Portsmouth), 1978-1979. (Box 14)
  - Communications Directory, 1978-1981. (Box 21)
  - Compensation Board, 1979. (Box 3)
  - Computerized Bill Status Access: Legislation, 1978-1979. (Box 6)
  - Computer Services, Dept. of, 1978-1979. (Box 3)
  - Consolidated Labs, Div. of, 1978. (Box 3)
  - Consolidated Personnel Report EPRI, 1978. (Box 32)
  - Consolidation Task Force, 1977. (Box 32)
  - Correctional Programs: Miscellaneous, 1976. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, 1974-1977. (Box 30)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Academy for Staff Development, 1980. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Adult Services Population Report, 1976-1980. (Box 24)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Agency Guide, 1980. (Box 31)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Air Conditioning Policy, 1976-1978. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Appalachian Learning Center 1977-1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Appeal Hearing (B. Joyce), 1978. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Barrett Learning Center, 1976-1977. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Beaumont Learning Center, 1976-1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Bon Air Intensive Treatment Learning Center #1, 1976-1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Bon Air Reception and Diagnostic Center, 1977-1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Booklets and Brochures, 1977-1978. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Budget, 1976-1977. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Camp New Hope, 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Caroline Correctional Unit Allegations of Improprieties, 1979-1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Centralization of Extradition Operations, 1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Chesapeake Juvenile, 1978. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Chesterfield Work Release Center, 1979-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Children Committed to the State Board of Corrections, 1974. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Coal Stockpile Reports, 1980-1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Communications System, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Community Youth Home, 1979. (Box 31)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Contracts, 1978-1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Correctional Field Unit #5 (Floyd), 1976. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Correctional Field Unit #6 (Woodbridge), 1977-1979. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Correctional Field Unit #7 (Robb, TV), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Correctional Field Unit #8 (Harrisonburg), 1978. (Box 8)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Correctional Field Unit #13 (Pocahontas), 1978-1980. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Correctional Field Unit #23 (Halifax), 1977-1981. (Box 8)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Correctional Field Units, Bureau of, 1976-1981. (Box 8)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Court Service Units/Placements, 1977-1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Death Row Inmates, 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Delinquency Prevention, 1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Determinate Sentencing, 1977. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Emotionally Disturbed Adults, 1977-1978. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Employee Complaints, 1978-1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Employment (Ombudsman), 1979. (Box 3)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Employment Practices, 1976. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Facilities (General), 1976-1979. (Box 26)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Fairfax Juvenile Detention Center, 1979. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Federal Standards for Corrections, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Finance, Div. of, 1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Food Service, 1978. (Box 14)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Forum on Issues in Corrections, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Gaudio, Anthony C., 1976-1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: General, 1976-1977. (Box 11)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: General, 1978. (Box 3)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: General, 1979. (Box 3)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: General, 1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: General (FBI), 1977. (Box 11)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Grievances (Special), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Grievances (Special): Craddock, Jane, 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Grievances (Special): Davis, Glen E., 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Guide for Minimum Standards for Planning, Design and Construction of Jail Facilities, 1974. (Box 31)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Hampton Arbitration Center, 1977. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Health Care Facilities, 1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Health Care for Inmates, 1977. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Health Care Inspection Reports Correspondence, 1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Heating Plant Summaries, 1978-1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Housing Alternatives, 1976-1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Housing Alternatives, 1979-1980. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Housing Plans for Clarke, Warren and Frederick Counties, 1976. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Incidents, 1978. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmate Labor Contracts with Localities, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmate Marriages, 1976-1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmate Mentality (Judge Thornton's Complaints), 1976. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmate Physical Exams, 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmate Population Projections, 1976-1978. (Box 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmate Review and Ad Hoc Committee, 1979. (Box 33)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmate Self-Mutilation, 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates, 1976-1980. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Abbitt, Jim), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Adams, Dennis O.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Adamson, Donald L.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Adkins, Lounzo), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Allen, Ernest L.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Allen, Richard C.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Arnistead, Ulric H.), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Asbury, James H., Jr.), 1976. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Atkinson, Charles W.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Baca, Linda R.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Banton, John), 1976-1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Batten, Reginald A.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Becker, Stephen), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Behrens, Ross E., and DiPalma / Ames), 1978-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Berger, John), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Berry, Dennis), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Bledsoe, Charles D.), 1977-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Boyer, Julian F.), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Brady, Andrew W.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Bragg, Oliver W.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Branham, Harry Jay), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Braxton, Ronald), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Breeden, James L.), 1976. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Briley, James), 1981. (Box 18)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Butler, George R.), 1978-1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Cadle, Ronald L.), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Campbell, Donald F.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Capsalis, John T.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Carpenter, Dewey), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Carr, Jeremiah), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Carrington, James M.), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Carter, Calvin R.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Carter, Donald M.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Carter, George W.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Carter, James), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Cartera, Harold W.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Cassidy, Rex), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Chaires, David), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Chandler, Alfred B., Jr.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Chaplin, James), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Childress, Garland L.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Clark, James T., Jr.), 1978-1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Clay, Robert L.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Coggins, Russell), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Colbert, Rodney E.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Cole, Carroll), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Coleman, J. Ferber), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Coleman, Lonnie E.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Collins, Bradford), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Coppola, Frank), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Cosby, Edward L.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Coulston, Archibald), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Dalson, Douglas R.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Dalton, Alvin), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Davenport, Darrell E.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Davidson, Paul M.), 1979-1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Davis, Wallace S.), 1978-1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Deagle, T. Elliot), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Deal, Dennis), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Deavers, James R.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (DeVore, Pete), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Dixon, Harold M.), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Dorn, Michael T.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Dorris, Harry W., Jr.), 1977. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Dowdell, Nish), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Drew, Joe L.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Driver, William), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Duff, Jimmy Ray, Jr.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Durham, William D.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Eadie, Joseph P.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Earles, Howard P.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Eason, Jimmie, III.), 1978. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Estes, Robert F.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Etheridge, David A.), 1976. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Faris, Wayne D.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Ferguson, Terry S.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Fisher, James), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Fitzgerald, Edward G.), 1979. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Font, Jorge A.), 1980. (Box 20)
  - Corrections, Dept. of: Inmates (Ford, Wilson), 1978. (Box 20)